<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on My website</title>
    <link>https://icebarf.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on My website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://icebarf.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Using CIMGUI</title>
      <link>https://icebarf.github.io/posts/cimgui_use/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icebarf.github.io/posts/cimgui_use/</guid>
      <description>Compile (static)  make static  Output will be present in current directory as libcimgui.a
Copy entire folder to wherever you wanna statically link then use the following commands in the compile command
-L ./cimgui -l:libcimgui.a Compile (Shared Library)  make all  Output will be present in current directory as cimgui.so
Copy entire folder to wherever you want and then link using follwing:
-L ./cimgui -lcimgui Using in C Define the following on top</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Implementing CDECL</title>
      <link>https://icebarf.github.io/posts/incomplete-implementation-cdecl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icebarf.github.io/posts/incomplete-implementation-cdecl/</guid>
      <description>Example input:
Example output: typer is a function returning a pointer to an array-of-int
How do we achieve this. First we have classify the input string and separate it out.
Input Size We&amp;rsquo;re gonna need a limit of how big declarations we can process, The ANSI C Standard specified a translation limit on how big a source line can be, that is 509 Lines. We&amp;rsquo;re gonna use 510 as the limit of out input string.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2D array with pointers</title>
      <link>https://icebarf.github.io/posts/2d-array-using-malloc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icebarf.github.io/posts/2d-array-using-malloc/</guid>
      <description>Concept In this case we&amp;rsquo;re not gonna be using as quote-on-quote multidimensional arrays. We&amp;rsquo;re gonna be using a pointer to an array and then Use the pointer offset &amp;ldquo;like&amp;rdquo; an array. Essentially what I am trying to get at is the follwing:
int (*my_arr)[] This declares my array as a pointer to an array of integers.
And to rid us of the confusion we&amp;rsquo;re gonna use a typedef some type to type[ARRAY]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Fresh Look on my website</title>
      <link>https://icebarf.github.io/posts/fresh_look/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icebarf.github.io/posts/fresh_look/</guid>
      <description>Deprecated While talking to a good friend of mine, He recommended me a static site generator called Hugo. It is a quite a powerful tool and has many themes and support for templates from other web programming languages/markup languages. I won&amp;rsquo;t go into much detail now but it is how it is. Anyways, we both found this cool theme that we&amp;rsquo;re using right now and it is called hugo.386. It took me about 2-3 Hours to configure everything right along with some trial and error on some areas and now we&amp;rsquo;re here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
